Izzy: Hi, Pamela.
Pamela: Hi, Izzy.
I thought I heard you.
Aren’t you working today?
Izzy: No, I took the day off.
Pamela: Are you OK?
Izzy: No.
Ben and I had a big argument last night.
Pamela: I’m sorry to hear that.
Have you been out today?
Izzy: No.
Pamela: Come on.
Let’s go for a walk.
Izzy: It was so embarrassing…and…
our relationship has been difficult recently.
I just don’t understand him anymore.
Pamela: Well…
sometimes people are difficult to understand.
Izzy: What’s his problem?
I have this great job.
I have this great opportunity.
Pamela: And…he’s just starting his career.
Izzy: Yeah.
I think you’re right.
I know what I want.
I know who I am.
Ben doesn’t.
He wants everything to stay the same.
It can’t all stay the same.
Life isn’t like that.
Pamela: So…Why don’t you tell that to him?
Ben: I thought you’d be here.
Izzy: Well, here I am.
Ben: I’m sorry.
I was an idiot.
Izzy: You were.
Ben: I don’t know why I didn’t tell you about Max earlier.
I didn’t tell you how I was feeling.
Izzy: I’m not interested in Max.
I never was.
He’s just my boss.
Ben: I know.
I know now.
Izzy: Look.
It’s my fault, too.
I’ve been so busy with my new job,
I didn’t have enough time to think about us.
I’m sorry.
Ben: Sure, I get it.
You’ve been busy and you’re doing really well.
I’m proud of you.
Izzy: Thanks.
I’m sorry if you feel like I’ve left you behind.
You’re so talented.
One day you’re going to be a great photographer.
Ben: Thanks.
You know…when we met we were in the same place in life.
Now we’re in very different places.
Izzy: I think you’re right.
This new job is really important to me.
It’s what I’ve always wanted to do.
Ben: Yeah.
You’ve found the right place for you.
But I don’t think your job leaves enough time for us.
Izzy: Yeah.
And…you need somebody who wants the same things as you want right now…
I don’t think I’m that person.
Ben: So is this it?
The end?
Izzy: I think so.
Ben: I think so, too.
We were really good together.
Izzy: We were.
Ben: You know that now my back’s better,
I could beat Max in a race, right?
Izzy: I know.